[
	{
		"question": "Where are you currently selling?",
		"height": "short",
		"shortenedQuestion": "Currently Selling",
		"answers": [
			{
				"id": 0,
				"text": "Amazon Seller Central",
				"optionIsSelected": false
			},
			{
				"id": 1,
				"text": "Amazon Vendor Central",
				"optionIsSelected": false
			},
			{
				"id": 2,
				"text": "Website",
				"optionIsSelected": false
			},
			{
				"id": 3,
				"text": "Amazon Vendor Express",
				"optionIsSelected": false
			},
			{
				"id": 4,
				"text": "other",
				"type": "textarea",
				"optionIsSelected": false
			}
		],
		"correct": 0,
		"feedback": "Lab916 are specialist in this service"
	},
	{
		"question": "What are some details about your Company?",
		"height": "medium",
		"shortenedQuestion": "Company Snapshot",
		"answers": [
			{
				"id": 0,
				"text": "Estimated Yearly Gross Sales All Channels?",
				"type": "input text",
				"optionIsSelected": false
			},
			{
				"id": 1,
				"text": "Estimate Monthly Gross Sales on Amazon?",
				"type": "input text",
				"optionIsSelected": false
			},
			{
				"id": 2,
				"text": "Annual marketing budget for Company?",
				"type": "input text",
				"optionIsSelected": false
			},
			{
				"id": 3,
				"text": "Monthly marketing budget on Amazon?",
				"type": "input text",
				"optionIsSelected": false
			}
		],
		"correct": 0,
		"feedback": "Lab916 are specialist in this service"
	},
	{
		"question": "What are the Goals you have for Amazon?",
		"height": "medium",
		"shortenedQuestion": "Amazon Goals",
		"answers": [
			{
				"id": 0,
				"text": "Summary of experience to date with Amazon (highlights and painpoints)?",
				"type": "textarea",
				"optionIsSelected": false
			},
			{
				"id": 1,
				"text": "Goals for Amazon Business",
				"type": "textarea",
				"optionIsSelected": false
			}
		],
		"correct": 0,
		"feedback": "Lab916 are specialist in this service"
	},
	{
		"question": "What services do you need help with?",
		"height": "extra short",
		"shortenedQuestion": "Amazon Services",
		"answers": [
			{
				"id": 0,
				"text": "Account Creation",
				"optionIsSelected": false
			},
			{
				"id": 1,
				"text": "Account Management",
				"optionIsSelected": false
			},
			{
				"id": 2,
				"text": "Content Creation (copywrite, images, enhanced content)",
				"optionIsSelected": false
			},
			{
				"id": 3,
				"text": "Inventory uploading and organization",
				"optionIsSelected": false
			},
			{
				"id": 4,
				"text": "Advertising",
				"optionIsSelected": false
			},
			{
				"id": 5,
				"text": "FBA Organization",
				"optionIsSelected": false
			},
			{
				"id": 6,
				"text": "Reviews",
				"optionIsSelected": false
			},
			{
				"id": 7,
				"text": "Expanding to other Amazon marketplaces",
				"optionIsSelected": false
			},
			{
				"id": 8,
				"text": "other",
				"type": "input text",
				"optionIsSelected": false
			}
		],
		"correct": 0,
		"feedback": "Lab916 are specialist in this service"
	},
	{
		"question": "A little bit more information about your Company",
		"height": "medium",
		"shortenedQuestion": "Other Questions",
		"answers": [
			{
				"id": 0,
				"text": "Link to your website/other online presence",
				"type": "textarea",
				"optionIsSelected": false
			},
			{
				"id": 1,
				"text": "Number of products in Company/Brand",
				"type": "input text",
				"optionIsSelected": false
			},
			{
				"id": 2,
				"text": "Number of products On Amazon",
				"type": "input text",
				"optionIsSelected": false
			}
		],
		"correct": 0,
		"feedback": "Lab916 are specialist in this service"
	}
]